<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: meta | Arrested DevOps]]></title>
  <link href="http://arresteddevops.com//blog/categories/meta/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://arresteddevops.com//"/>
  <updated>2013-12-05T19:33:23-06:00</updated>
  <id>http://arresteddevops.com//</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Arrested DevOps]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[If this, then that]]></title>
    <link href="http://arresteddevops.com//2013/12/04/if-this/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-04T10:23:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://arresteddevops.com//2013/12/04/if-this</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First thing I learned? When using the rake task of &ldquo;new_post&rdquo; in Octopress, don&rsquo;t include a comma. It loses it.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;m writing this post to make sure our <a href="https://ifttt.com">if this then that</a> recipe is working. It also seemed like a fun time to try out the <a href="https://github.com/scottwb/jekyll-tweet-tag">Liquid Tweet Tag for Jekyll and Octopress</a> that I just put into the code.</p>

<p><div class='embed tweet'>Tweet could not be processed</div>
<div class='embed tweet'>Tweet could not be processed</div></p>

<p>Nifty, huh?</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Titles are hard]]></title>
    <link href="http://arresteddevops.com//2013/12/03/titles-are-hard/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-03T21:14:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://arresteddevops.com//2013/12/03/titles-are-hard</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As of the time of this post, the subhead of Arrested DevOps is &ldquo;DevOps Podcast for fun but no profit&rdquo;. Which is there mostly as a placeholder, as so much of the AD stuff is right now. But that&rsquo;s not really a good subhead. Or a tagline. Or a way to summarize what Arrested DevOps is about.</p>

<p>We&rsquo;ll be (hopefully) recording our first podcast on Thursday. Which is two days from now. We need a tagline by then, just to help people understand what we are about. And as much as I love the name and the riff on Arrested Development, I don&rsquo;t want to use that in the tagline.</p>

<p>Fundamentally, our goal is to be accessible, friendly to people new to the concepts, and very devoid of &ldquo;inside baseball&rdquo;. And also to not make people feel dirty for using Microsoft products. Any ideas for a great tagline? Please either tweet use at <a href="https://www.twitter.com/arresteddevops">@arresteddevops</a> or leave your thoughts in the comments.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[It has begun...]]></title>
    <link href="http://arresteddevops.com//2013/11/21/it-has-begun-dot-dot-dot/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-21T19:27:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://arresteddevops.com//2013/11/21/it-has-begun-dot-dot-dot</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The world definitely needs another DevOps podcast. We&rsquo;re still working out what exactly we&rsquo;ll be covering. Right now, the main reason this site is up is that <a href="https://twitter.com/mattstratton">Matt</a> is trying to play around with <a href="http://www.octopress.org">Octopress</a> and get some stuff working all fancy-like.</p>

<p>But how did this happen? I&rsquo;m a big fan of a few great DevOps type podcasts, most notably the following:</p>

<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.theshipshow.com">The Ship Show</a></li>
<li><a href="http://foodfightshow.org/">Food Fight</a></li>
<li><a href="http://devopscafe.org/">DevOps Cafe</a></li>
</ul>


<p>With so much great content out there, why do we need another one? One thing that came to mind is that, for better or for worse, these podcasts have a very heavy FOSS focus to them. Which is fine, because FOSS is pretty cool. But there&rsquo;s a lot of Windows out there in the real world as well. It seemed that there were more voices to be heard. Which basically maeans that I want you to hear <strong>my</strong> voice.</p>

<p>I&rsquo;ve had this domain for a bit, and always intended to create a blog here. However, a podcast seemed like a cool idea. Especially since I&rsquo;ve never done one before. But I wasn&rsquo;t about to do one myself. Because, well, I&rsquo;m kind of lazy. Also, I&rsquo;m the &ldquo;Ops&rdquo; in &ldquo;DevOps&rdquo;, and that makes for a one-sided conversation.</p>

<p>I met <a href="https://twitter.com/trevorghess">Trevor</a> at the <a href="http://www.meetup.com/Downtown-Chicago-Azure-Meet-Up/">Downtown Chicago Azure Meet-Up</a> back in October, and he presented about Continuous Integration at the next month&rsquo;s meetup. Of course, I completely steamrolled everything he had to say, which is why I immediately thought of him as someone to do a podcast with.</p>

<p>We don&rsquo;t know what this will be yet. Watch this space for updates. I don&rsquo;t expect that your professional life will change or your organization will achieve amazing levels of productivity just based on anything we say, but hopefully you&rsquo;ll enjoy it once we have something.</p>

<p>One thing I can guarantee: Lots of Doctor Who references.</p>

<p><strong><em>What would you like to hear on a DevOps podcast? Thoughts on this in general? Let us know in the comments!</em></strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
